# **Bradfield Phillips**

# **Software Developer**

C 074 - 780 4906 M hello@bradfield-dev.com M Portfolio Website

# Contact

1 Harpuisboom Single Eikenbosch, Kuils River Cape Town, South Africa 7580

LinkedIn Profile

# **Key Skills**

C# HTML, CSS MS SQL Server JavaScript, Razor & MVC Unit testing

# Activities and Interests

Rugby Hiking Formula 1 Lego's Reading Dev Tech articles

# Overview

Self-directed and motivated Software Developer with 3 years' experience building client-facing web and mobile applications and internal tools. As a full time developer at Viridian International, I worked alongside senior developers and was trusted with development, code review(s), and live release testing and deployment of a high-profile, consumer-facing web application.

# **Experience**

March 2021 — Present

Software Developer • Veridian International • Cape Town, South Africa

Planning & Tasks | Stand-Up Sessions | Sprint Runs | Code review(s)
& Unit tests | Push & Deploy to Trunk.

March 2020 — June 2021

Desktop Support (Contractor) • Allan Gray Proprietary Limited • Cape Town, South Africa

- Assist Desktop team with planning and profiling users workstations | Provide L2 hardware and software support

December 2017 — March 2021

System Administrator • Computer Technolink • Cape Town, South Africa

 Undertake small to medium-sized IT projects | Provide L3 hardware and software support

## Education

## Microsoft Azure

March 2022 - Present

Bagged AZ-900. Currently preparing for AZ-204

#### Harvard [CS50]

March 2019 – Jan 2020

Participated in David J Malan Computer Science online virtual series.

#### Clever Programmer

April 2020 – September 2021

- Self-investment during the early stages of the Pandemic. **TechStack**: JavaScript, HTML & CSS, React Native. **Projects**: Google Maps Web App, COVID-19 tracker and HackeRank competitions, to name a few.

#### Self-taught education

W3Schools, Code Academy, Udemy & .NET Design Patterns In C#